websitevalued.com 2010-11-20

# WebsiteValued.com Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

WebsiteValued.com is an Australian internet based service run by Gary Brewer (ABN: 49 610 791 313)

**Key Points:**

 **
  * We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
**

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

#### (1) What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

(a) information about your visits to and use of this website;

(b) information about any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;

(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us and/or subscribing to our website services and/or email notifications;

#### (2) Information about website visits

We may collect information about you computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. We may use this information in the administration of this website, to improve the website's usability, and for marketing purposes.

#### (3) Using your personal data

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may use your personal information to:

(a) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;

(b) to contact you about features and updates about WebsiteValued.com exclusively.

#### (4) Other disclosures

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and

(d) to the purchaser or seller (or prospective purchaser or seller) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling or purchasing.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

#### (6) Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

If you create an account, you are responsible for keeping your password confidential. We will not ask you for your password.

#### (7) Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

#### (8) Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at 60 Australian Dollars).

#### (9) Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content, terms and conditions or privacy policies of third party websites.

#### (10) Cookies

This site uses cookies for the purpose of remembering who you are when you return to the site.

#### (11) Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to privacy@websitevalued.com or write to us at - 

PO BOX 290  
Manly, NSW 1655  
AUSTRALIA

Back
